Cheryl H. D'Avignon

184 Williams Street Meriden, CT 06450 203-605-9333 bfly0104@yahoo.com

Summary of Qualifications:

Highly responsible, reliable and motivated office professional who adapts well to all work situations.

Demonstrates great customer service skills and organizational abilities.

Background consists of last 15 years in an education/corporate setting processing high volume and high quality work for corporate staff and students.

Able to follow federal and state regulations and policies to process work in a timely, efficient manner.

Fast learner and flexible, an independent worker

Tactful team player

Able to multitask and prioritize in a high pressure, meet-deadline sort of environment.

Education:

Bachelor of Arts, May 1989 Messiah College, Grantham, PA

Major: Family Studies Minor: Early Childhood Education

Relevant Experience:

April 2000 - April 2012

Bursar for Business Office (Student Accounts)

Premier Education Group East Haven, CT 06512

- *Perform refund calculations for all withdrawn students for 7 schools
- *Follow policies and procedures to perform tasks regarding federal and state regulations
- *Answer phone calls concerning student accounts, refund calculation explanations and financial aid.
- *Post financial aid disbursements and student payments to student accounts.
- *Maintained and audited student ledger cards
- *Help with monthly closeouts for all of Premier Education Group schools to comply with federal and school policy.

July 1996 - April 2000

Financial Aid Director

Premier Education Group Windsor and Southington campuses in Connecticut

- *Supervised financial aid officers in the interviewing process and helped answer questions regarding the process of determining eligibility and their financial aid package.
- *Interviewed students to determine the amount of financial aid based on students' needs and available funds.
- *Responsible for maintaining all financial aid files (active and inactive) with information that was in compliance with state and federal regulations.
- *Print start date reports and remaining balance to schedule reports to make sure students were packaged with financial aid and were paperwork ready to start school.
- *Utilized software systems such as CLASS (school database), Word and Excel.

Other Experience:

August 1994 - Financial Aid Officer

April 1996 Connecticut Business Institute North Haven, CT 06473

Nov. 1993 - Financial Aid Officer

August 1994 Technical Careers Institute West Haven, CT 06516

*Interviewed students applying for financial aid, including loans and grants, to determine eligibility for assistance.

*Maintain all student files and student accounts

July 1991 - Data Capture Specialist

Nov. 1993 Computard International Inc. Trumbull, CT 06611

*Operated keyboard to enter alphabetic and numeric data from source documents into computer following format displayed on screen. (65 wpm)

*Compiled, sorted, and verified accuracy of data entered.

*Assisted lead operators in running edits and recording work completed.

Nov. 1992 - Transcriber

September 1993 Sacred Heart University, Dr. Cindy Eberhart, Fairfield, CT

*Typed interview information from micro cassettes onto a personal computer using a transcription machine.

*Printed out information and delivered to her office.

Summer 1988, Secretary/Clerk

Thermal Acoustics, Inc. West Haven, CT 06516

*Answered phones, typed forms and documents, typed correspondence, filed, invoicing, and worked with various office machines

*Assisted bookkeeper with basic accounting tasks.

References Available Upon Request

Summer 1988 May 1989 -Jan 1991